Contact

stephpretty@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-pretty-5a1698113 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HeartMate 3

ECMO

Impella

Honors-Awards

2019 SONSIEL Hackathon Winner-Team Night Vision

Stephanie Pretty

B.S.N., R.N., CCRN, CSCRN; Nurse Innovator and Entrepreneur Boston, Massachusetts

Summary

Registered nurse of ten years, currently employed in the cardiac SICU at Brigham and Women's Hospital. Nationally certified in critical care, progressive care, cardiac and cardiac-surgical nursing.

Through my passion for art and science, I have recently discovered a strong interest in innovation, design, and problem-solving which has inspired me to enter the world of entrepreneurship. I hope to one day bring my experience, talents, and ideas to a larger scale of healthcare professionals in both the U.S. and globally.

Experience

Brigham and Women's Hospital Critical Care Registered Nurse March 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months) Greater Boston Area

Cardiovascular Surgical ICU

Jersey Shore University Medical Center 4 years

Critical Care RN 2016 - 2018 (2 years)

Neptune, New Jersey

(Float Pool)

Medical ICU, Surgical/Trauma ICU, Cardiac Care Unit, Neuro/Neuro-Surgical ICU, Cardiovascular Surgery ICU, Pediatric ICU

Critical Care RN 2014 - 2016 (2 years) Joint Medical ICU and Cardiac Care Unit

Aya Healthcare
Travel RN
October 2016 - March 2017 (6 months)

Greater Boston Area

Brigham and Women's Health (Float Pool)

Medical ICU, Coronary Care Unit, Neuro/Neuro-Surgical ICU, Surgical/Burn/ Trauma ICU, Cardiac Curgery ICU, Thoracic ICU, All progressive care and med-surg units

Southern Ocean County Hospital Emergency Room Registered Nurse 2013 - 2014 (1 year)

ER

Community Medical Center-Toms River, NJ Critical Care RN 2011 - 2014 (3 years) Telemetry/Progressive Care/Med-Surg

MONOC

EMT

2008 - 2011 (3 years)

Surgical/Medical ICU

911 and SCT/Critical Care transport

East Dover First Aid Squad EMT 2007 - 2011 (4 years)

Volunteer EMT

Education

Ocean County College

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2007 - 2010)

Kean University

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2013 - 2016)